newsx.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy - NewsX

At **NewsX.com** , the English news website of NewsX news channel of the ITV  
Network, we respect your privacy immensely. Consequently, when you visit our  
website(s) we don’t collect your personal data unless you are ready to  
provide the information to us. Here, we outline what we do with information  
provided to us by readers.

**Information Collected and Stored Automatically**

If you visit NewsX.com just to browse or read or download information, we  
don’t gather or store info. If you register for our services, we do store  
some information automatically though this would not record your identity.

Usually, we collect information on the browser you use (e.g. Firefox, Google  
Chrome, Edge), the operating system your computer, mobile runs and your  
Internet Service Provider’s domain name, the date and time of your visit and  
the pages you see. We use this non-personal identifiable information, though  
not all the time, to improve the design and content of our website, and to  
give you an easier browsing experience.

**What Personal Data Do We Collect?**

Only if you volunteer it, we store your name, address, e-mail address, your  
interests and the services you are subscribed for. This information you  
provide is not shared, given or sold to any other private organisation or  
persons.

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**

Our website(s) can have links to other websites which may have different  
privacy policies. Since we have no control over them, users should consult  
the privacy notices of other sites’ privacy notices. We use a third party to  
serve ads on our pages, when showing the ads, our third-party advertiser may  
place or recognise a unique “cookie” on your browser and may use information  
(not including your name, address, e-mail address) about your visits to this  
and other websites to serve ads of interest to you.

**Opting out**

If a user opts out from using the Ads Settings, the unique DoubleClick  
cookie ID on the user’s browser is overwritten with “OPT_OUT”. Because there  
is no longer a unique cookie ID, the opt-out cookie can’t be associated with  
a particular browser.

**If you have complaints, please give us the following information in your**  
**request:**

1\. Full name with postal residential address, mobile number and email id.  
2\. The title-headline, date/link of news report, article or content which  
you wish to complain against, including identification of information  
provided by you.  
3\. Clear statement as to whether the information is personal or sensitive  
personal information.  
4\. Specify what supporting documents, if any are relied upon and attached.  
5\. A declaration that whatever information and/or documents are submitted  
with the complaint are true, complete and current in all respects and  
nothing therein is false.  
6\. A statement, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notice  
is accurate, and that the information in the complaint is yours.  
7\. You may also contact us in case you have any questions/ suggestions about

We use third-party advertising companies to serve the ads displayed on our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email or phone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

the Privacy Policy using the contact information mentioned above.

The company shall not be responsible for any communication, if addressed, to  
any non-designated person in this regard.

Please note that the complaint must be from someone personally and directly  
affected by the matter.
